

CONTACT

STATEMENT

kimandy703@gmail.com 703 399 6134

> kimandy.net github.com/alienk703

Full stack developer and design enthusiast with a sensitivity to the user experience. Creative technologist who inspires and motivates others to achieve success. Laser-focused commitment to meet and exceed goals to develop responsive and functional web applications.

SKILLS

EDUCATION

Ruby, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript, jQuery Backbone.js, PostgreSQL AJAX, CSS & HTML

Object Oriented Programing TDD/EDD, API Integration Wireframing, Data Modeling, Photoshop & Illustrator

Fluent in Korean and Japanese

GENERAL ASSEMBLY (2014)

Web Development Immersive

Full-stack web development program focused on common best practices in object-oriented programming, MVC frameworks, data modeling, and test-driven development. Developed a portfolio of individually focused and collaboratively focused projects.

TEMPLE UNIVERSITY (2004~2009) Bachelor of Arts

Broadcasting Telecommunication Mass Media Concentration, Music Industry Philadelphia, PA

Washington DC

INTERESTS

EXPERIENCE

Music Production, Bass Guitar, Movies Fantasy Sports Sports Spectating MBC TV NEWS (2012~2014)

Associate News Producer

- * Coordinated credentials, interviews, news transcriptions, video research news research and office administration
- * Filmed and edited video footage using ENG camera equipment

EMPIRE ENTERTAINMENT JAPAN (2008~2012)

Tokyo, Japan

Washington DC

Special Events Producer/Graphic Designer

- * Produced various events to include: seminars, product launch, corporate parties, fashion show, live performances
- * Designed event posters, invitations, flyers, PowerPoints and Keynote presentations
- * Managed event budgeting, coordination and special talent casting